privatecash.com 2006-06-15

# Private Cash

**Coldfair Holdings Ltd. Privacy Policy**

Coldfair Holdings Ltd. (referred to as 'Coldfair') knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Private.com and any of the sites in the Coldfair family (as described in paragraph x), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

What this privacy policy covers   
· This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that collects when you are on the web site, and when you user's services. This policy also covers treatment of any personally identifiable information that 's business partners share with or that may collect on a partner's site. 

· This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Coldfair does not own or control, or to people that Coldfair does not employ or manage. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact the Privacy Manager by email at [info@privateCS.com](mailto:info@privateCS.com)

**Information Collection and Use**

Coldfair is the sole owner of the information collected on www.private.com. Coldfair collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration**

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address) and unique identifiers (such as, username and password). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Order**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

\- Log in to access your personal account or \- Send an email to Customer Service here: [support@privateCS.com](mailto:support@privateCS.com)

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have view the adult warning page or choose their preference of language, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user's language preference would not be saved. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Users may opt-out of these communications. Please see our Choice and Opt-out section.

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) We do share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information: 

**We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties.**

In compliance with Title 18 U.S.C. Section 2257. All models over 18, proof of age on file with G. Leonardi , Private North America, 10947 Pendleton St. Sun Valley, Ca. 91352 

**Third Party Intermediaries**

We sometimes use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Service Providers**

We partner with other third parties, RoundPoint for PrivatePDA, to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Business Transitions**

In the event Coldfair goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or by going to this link or the user may contact us at email at support@privateCS.com to opt-out. 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Coldfair, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code). Contact information will be to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Coldfair will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Coldfair stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Coldfair at [support@privateCS.com](mailto:support@privateCS.com) to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Chat Rooms**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [support@privateCS.com](mailto:support@privateCS.com)

Supplementation of Information In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

**Address Verification**

ID/Address verification is necessary in the case of returned packages, replacements and credit card payments for certain countries (countries specified in shop). We verify by contacting the customer.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at [support@privateCS.com](mailto:support@privateCS.com)

**Notification of Changes**

This privacy policy covers the following Coldfair Web sites: 

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

Privacy Policy Manager  
Coldfair Holdings Ltd.  
36, Vyronos Avenue  
Nicosia Tower Center  
2nd Floor  
Office 201  
1096 Nicosia Cyprus

Email: support@privateCS.com
